<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DocaApp</string>
    <string name="menu_home">Home</string>
    <string name="menu_product">Products</string>
    <string name="menu_profile">Profile</string>
    <string name="howto_vet">Vet visits for young adult dogs\nAt this stage in your dog’s life, your vet may recommend baseline blood work and a urinalysis. Depending on their environment, a heartworm test and/or tick-borne disease screen may be performed at least annually along with fecal ova and parasite testing.\n\nSome congenital health concerns can be easier to evaluate as your dog gets older, so your vet may check for certain heart defects, ocular abnormalities, retained testicles, and orthopedic issues.\n\nThis may also be the best time to discuss the optimal time to spay or neuter your dog, based on your dog’s size, breed(s), and lifestyle.</string>
    <string name="howto_exercise">Young adulthood may be a great time to add swimming, running, agility classes, and hiking to your dog’s activities, if you haven’t already. \n\nIntroduce new activities slowly and with supervision. Young adult dogs may still not always know what’s dangerous and what is not. Keep a close eye on your dog to avoid injury or accidents.</string>
    <string name="howto_dental">Talk to your vet about your at-home oral hygiene routine and the recommended frequency of dental cleanings. They may recommend tooth brushing, sprays, gels, water additives, food, and/or treats that have been accepted by the Veterinary Oral Health Council to decrease plaque and calculus accumulation.\n\nSmaller dogs likely have a level of dental care and prevention that is more involved than that of a larger dog. Muzzle shape also plays an important role.\n\nFor small and medium-sized dogs, the American Animal Hospital Association’s (AAHA) guidelines recommend a complete dental prophylaxis (cleaning, polishing, and examination under general anesthesia) by one year of age.  For large or giant dogs, this is recommended by two years of age. Talk to your veterinarian about the recommended frequency of dental prophylaxis treatments.</string>
    <string name="howto_nutrition">Young adulthood is the time to continue (or establish) healthy habits and a consistent feeding schedule. This is also the time to transition from a growth (puppy) food to a maintenance (adult) diet.\n\nObesity is one of the largest contributors to morbidity and mortality as a dog ages. Fat itself is not an inactive substance in the body. It plays a role in hormonal regulation, inflammation, and other disease processes.\n\nSome breeds may benefit from a lower-fat diet while others may need a special diet to decrease the risk of bladder stones. A veterinarian will assess a dog’s body condition and muscle mass and advise if your dog’s diet needs to be adjusted. Dogs that are spayed and neutered typically require fewer calories than dogs that remain intact. Discuss this with your veterinarian.</string>
</resources>